integration, making friends. A.
Daniel found a story about friends.
Read the story with him and answer the questions below.
Two friends and the bear.
Two friends were walking in the forest.
It was a sunny day and they were happy.
Suddenly they saw a bear coming towards them.
They were very scared.
One of the friends quickly climbed up a tree.
The other tried too, but he failed.
He knew he couldn't fight the bear alone, so he lay down on the ground.
He thought, the bear will leave me alone if it thinks I'm dead.
The bear came close to the friend on the ground and smelt his head, but it didn't attack.
After the bear left, the other friend came down from the tree.
It looked like the bear said something to you, he said.
Yes, answered the friend on the ground.
It said a true friend should not leave you in times of danger.